Did you manage to do it in the end?
結局できた?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
I agree.
そうだね
how was it?
どうだった?
Was it hard just now?
さっききつかった?
tired?
疲れた?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Do you always masturbate?
いつもオナリンとかする?
I don't.
しないんだ
I see.
なるほど
If I were to masturbate, I wonder how it would feel.
もしさ、オナリンするとしたら、 どんな感じにするかちょっと
Can I have it done?
やって もらっていい?
can.
できる
Maybe I can do it.
できるかも
Onarin is 20 kg.
オナリン20キロだよ
can?
できる?
Yes, that's fine.
はい、でいいよ
Now, let me take off your shirt for a second.
じゃあ、ちょっとシャツをはどけさせてください
good?
いい?
It's Masaru.
マサルじゃん
So, feel free to touch it yourself.
じゃあ、自分でちょっと触ってください
Oh, wait.
あ、 待って
myself?
自分?
It's refreshing.
リグッとしてるじゃん
Should I just take out the legs?
足だけ抜いちゃうか
Give it a good jerk.
しっかりグッと
Please start showing your butt.
お尻つきだしてください
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's fine facing this way.
こっち向きでいいよ
Yeah, that's right.
うん、そうそう
So, spread your legs yourself.
で、足自分で広げて
Well then, touch me a little.
じゃあ、ちょっと口触って
difficult?
難しい?
It's not like we're naughty.
僕らでやらしくないよ
I'll do it intensely.
激しくするよ
I should have said it earlier.
さっき言ったらいい
Yo.
よ
Good, that's good.
いい ね、それいいよ
I feel like my butt is twitching.
なんかお尻ひくひくしてるね
Would you like to do some exercise?
体操してごらん?
Move it once.
一回動かして
Open and close your butt.
お尻開いたり閉じたりして
Have you ever had your butt played with?
お尻ってさ、 いじられたりしたことある?
That's right.
そうだよね
Did you know that your butt can make you feel good?
お尻で気持ちよくなれるの知ってる?
Yeah.
うん
i don't know?
知らない?
Are you a little curious about butts?
お尻にちょっと興味ある?
It's okay to touch the chest.
くりとり触ってていいよ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くはない?
Yeah.
うん
Don't you know?
わかんない?
It's all in now.
全部入っちゃってる、今の
Look, I've got all this.
ほら、これ全部入っちゃった
Don't you know?
わかんない?
It fit perfectly.
全然すっぽり入っちゃったよ
That's plenty of room.
余裕だね
That's not it.
ああじゃないよ
How do you feel when you leave?
出るときどんな感じ?
Do you want to put it out?
出したくなる?
You can take it out.
出していいよ
I feel like I need to go to the toilet.
トイレしたくなる感じなんだ
This is already an easy win.
これはもう楽勝だね
This feels kind of unsettling.
なんか不安な感じだ、これは
It's easy to get in.
簡単に入ってるね
There's only one more thing left, so relax and take a deep breath.
さっきのが後1個で 力を抜いて深呼吸して
Do you know what's in there?
入 ってるのわかる?
amazing.
すごい
It didn't hurt, right?
痛くなかったでしょ?
I have a feeling.
余感はある
It feels weird when it comes off.
抜けるとき変な感じだよね
All of this was included.
これ全部入ってたよ
Not just a little.
ちょっとじゃない
Just a moment.
ちょっとって
I just don't understand.
ちょっとわかんない
Do you know what's in there?
入ってるのわかる?
Can you see it moving?
動いてるのわかる?
I'm taking it in and out a lot.
めっちゃ出し入れしてるよ
I want to take a deep breath.
深呼吸したいし
Touch it slowly.
ゆっくり触って
But it didn't hurt at all, right?
でも全然痛くなかったでしょ?
I can see it a little.
ちょっと見えちゃってる
You don't have to see it yet.
まだ見なくていいよ
I don't see it.
見ない
I've been doing it for a day.
1日やってるね
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
tell me.
教えて
It feels weird.
変な感じ
It's painful.
苦しいね
That would be awesome, if you could get it in like this.
やばいね、これで入れられたら
This is tough.
きついね、これ
Yuutsu, that's terrible.
ゆうつ、やばいね
I'm taking a deep breath.
結構でも深呼吸入ってるね
stop
休
Rest.
憩
Finally, let's move it violently and finish it off.
最後、 激しく動かして終わりにしようか
Finally, let's move it vigorously and finish it off.
最後、激しく動かして終わりにしよう
Are you going to put your butt inside?
お尻を中に入れていく?